allmemoirs.com 2013-06-08

# allMemoirs Privacy Policy

allMemoirs Privacy Policy

allMemoirs respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect, how we use that information, and what choices you have.  
Please take a few moments to read this agreement. By accessing allMemoirs, you agree to accept the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and are aware that our policies may evolve in the future as indicated below. 

What Information is collected?

Your name, email address, gender, timezone and locale.  
(Since the only way to login is through Facebook, this information is fetched from your Facebook profile.)  
Your Friend list from Facebook.  
Your Phone details like Model, Operating System and Screen Size, when accessing allMemoirs from the Mobile.  
Your Facebook password is **never** collected by allMemoirs.  

How is the Information used?

To provide a personalized experience when using allMemoirs.  
To share your allMemoirs updates with your Friends.  
To monitor and analyze usage and trends to increase the functionality of our Services.  
To send notifications regarding activity on your allMemoirs and other such administrative and operational updates.  

What information is shared?

Based on your Sharing Settings, your feed updates will be posted to your Friends on allMemoirs.  
Your Personal Information will never be shared with any Third Party without your consent.  
If your product becomes popular or is a rare find, and is publicly available in the Internet domain, it gets shared with other Users as part of Popular Trends.  

How does Sharing work?

By default, your updates (Products, Wishlist, Shops) will be shared on allMemoirs.  
You can decide to not share your allMemoirs updates.  
By default, your updates will be shared on allMemoirs with your Friends of Friends.  
You can decide to change this to Friends only.  
Sharing options are applicable for updates made after the settings have been updated.  
Older updates are governed by the Sharing option applicable at the time of the update.
